To get the story, they’ll risk everything.
Welcome to Sarajevo is a war, drama, history film
directed by Michael Winterbottom.
Follow a group of international journalists into the heart of the once cosmopolitan city of
Sarajevo—now a danger zone of sniper and mortar attacks where residents still live.
While reporting on an American aid worker who’s trying to get children out of the country,
a British correspondent decides to take an orphaned girl home to London.
Michael Henderson, played by Stephen Dillane.
Flynn, played by Woody Harrelson.
Nina, played by Marisa Tomei.
Risto Bavić, played by Goran Višnjić.
Emira, played by Emira Nušević.
Jane Carson, played by Kerry Fox.
Welcome to Sarajevo is a 1997 war drama film directed by Michael Winterbottom, written by Frank
Cottrell Boyce and is based on the book Natasha's Story by Michael Nicholson.
The film stars Stephen Dillane, Woody Harrelson, Marisa Tomei, Emira
Nušević, Kerry Fox, Goran Višnjić, James Nesbitt, and Emily Lloyd.
Welcome to Sarajevo had its world premieres at Cannes and the Toronto International Film Festival in May and September 1997, and was released in
the United Kingdom on 21 November 1997, by FilmFour Distributors, and in the United States on 26 November 1997, by Miramax Films.
The film explores themes of journalist, civil war,
england, orphanage, bosnian war (1992-95).
The tone is emotional.